wyo.in 2016-10-16

# Privacy Policy – Wear Your Opinion - WYO.in

You know, we at WYO are geeks, too. And like all good geeks, we’re obsessed with privacy. We won’t share or sell your personal information for a quick buck. And we promise we will never collect or share information about your IQ, your religious beliefs, your shoe size, or how you got that intriguing scar on your left elbow. In general terms, we collect information so we can ship your WYOs, let you enjoy our community features, and improve our website, services, and products.

Or, in legalese...

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. This contains important information about your rights and obligations. This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which Shreenath Lifestyle Private Limited (“WYO”, “We”, “Us” and “Our”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from Users (each, a “User” also referred to as “You” and “Yours”) of the website [www.wyo.in](http://www.wyo.in/) (“Website”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Website and all services offered by Us through the Website. By entering and using the Website, You are consenting to the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy please do not avail, use or register our Site.

We may revise the Privacy Policy at any time by updating this page. By registering or using our Site, You agree to be bound by any such changes. You can view our updated Privacy Policy by visiting [here](http://wyo.in/pages/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy"):

  1. **INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU:**

**Personal identification information:**

We may collect Your personal information in various ways while You use or access our Website.  We may collect your personal identification information such as name, email id, mailing address, phone number, credit card information that you may enter while registering with the Website or while interacting with our customer representatives. You may visit our Website anonymously without registering with our Website. We will collect Your personal identification information only if You voluntarily submit such information to us. You may refuse to supply personal identification, except that it may prevent You from fully utilizing the Website. 

**Non-personal Identification Information:**

We may collect certain non-personal identification information about You, whenever You interact without Website. Non-personal identification information may include without limitation browser name, version, the type of device used, operating system and version, website or service that referred used to the Website, language preference, location information, technical information and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance user experience or sometimes to personalize user experience. A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on Your computer's hard drive. Cookie helps in analyzing web traffic or lets us know when You visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to Your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about Your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps Us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our Website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

Overall, cookies help Us provide You with a better Website, by enabling Us to monitor which pages You find useful and which You do not. A cookie in no way gives Us access to Your computer or any information about You, other than the data You choose to share with Us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but You may manually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent You from taking full advantage of the Website **.**

  2. **HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION:**

We may collect and use Your personal information for the following purposes:

  * We may use information to control your access to Our Site and services, to communicate with you, customize your experience by providing information that may be useful or interesting based on the content and personally identifiable information relating to you.

  * We may use the email address to send Users information, administrative information, changes in account settings, changes to our services or updating you on new policies and updates pertaining to your order. Apart from this if Users choose to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive periodic emails that may relate to company news, related product or service information, etc Email address may also be used for responding to any of your inquiries, questions, and/or any other requests. If You want to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from Us, please follow the “Unsubscribe” instructions provided at the bottom of each email.

  * We may use the information Users provide about them while placing an order, only to complete said order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

  * We may use the Users information to analyse the use of the Website, and the people visiting and using the Website for the improving the features of the Website. Further, the information provided by You may also be used to help Us in responding to Your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

  * We may also use Your information for market research purposes and may share your information with our affiliated business for the said purpose.

  * We may also share Your information with any third parties including any government departments if the disclosure of such information is required by law or is based on any order by a court of competent jurisdiction.

  3. **HOW WYO PROTECTS YOUR INFORMATION?**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect Your personal information against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction . Sensitive and private data exchange between the Website and the users happen over a SSL (Secure Socket Layer) secured communication channel.

However, We cannot guarantee the security of any information obtained through unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors that may compromise the security of the information. It is important for You to prevent unauthorized access to Your account by limiting access to Your device.

  4. **SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We do not sell, **trade, or rent Users personal i** dentification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Information posted and shared on the Website or on our social media pages by the User with an intention to publish and share with the public can be seen by anyone including search engines hence care must be exercised while submitting.  This information includes anything User chooses to publish, post or submit on the Website or our Social Media Pages including photos and images.

  5. **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

We may update and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted as notification on the main page of our Website on this link ___________. Users are encouraged to periodically check this page to stay informed about changes to our Privacy Policy. The revised Policy will be effective from the date stated on the revised Privacy Policy. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications. If you disagree to any of the changes to the Privacy Policy, please refrain from using or availing the services of the Website. Your continued use or availing of the Website following the posting of revised Policy will indicate your acceptance and acknowledgement of the changes and you will be bound by it.

  6. **CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, Please contact us at info@wyo.in

This document was last updated on 29nd January 2016
